Education is what remains after one has forgotten what one has learned in school.
Yeah.
Joshua.
Okay.
Good.
All right.
So what have we done so far?
We've been putting together a fascinating little interesting site with some education quotes, but I
reckon we can make this better.
Yeah, definitely can make this better.
What do you think we'll be needing here?
Um.
Some formatting.
Yeah, I think we need to change it up a bit just to make them look like quotes.
Not just like.
Yeah, it's a bit boring there.
So maybe let's consider what happens if we, like, sort of, um, this part here.
You know, the actual quote.
If we put that in italics, could we do that?
Yes.
Okay.
So let's get the quotes in italics.
So to make italics all we got to do is make sure you put a space in.
Then we put our I and then tab it in and you'll see we've got our eye for eye italics.
Yeah.
So that's pretty easy.
Eye for italics.
Okay.
So let's put the You know, not the whole thing.
Let's just put the the the quotes in italics, and I think we should, uh, uh, see how that looks.
Yeah.
Like that.
Yeah, that's very good.
Yes, but what about me?
Uh, Nelson Mandela?
I also want to have the italics for my quote.
I want to see how you change the world.
Okay?
Yeah, yeah.
What about me?
I'm Benjamin Franklin, and I also want to tell it for my quote.
Yeah, so he can put it.
Yeah.
Come on, man, get on with it.
All of them.
Yeah.
We all want to have italics for our quotes.
Um, there we go.
Come on Benjamin.
No.
No, nothing.
Uh, now we can also for this one we haven't got any break so we can look what remains after what remains
after a break.
Yeah, that is good.
I like to have a break sometimes.
Yes.
Um, then I'll put another.
I'll put another break there.
you are very good.
You save this.
All right.
Let's have a look at.
Okay.
It looks a bit better.
Oh.
Benjamin Franklin.
His name is in italics.
Oof!
Okay.
Yeah.
We've put this too early.
Too late.
So you can see how important it is.
Also trying to see where your tags are going.
Um, and obviously, it's not that difficult to quickly see.
Ah, right.
So now we've got just the quotes.
Let's put Albert Einstein's name on the next line.
You see, at the moment his name is on the same line.
So what do we need there?
We need another beer.
Okay.
So hit enter.
So it goes on to the next line.
So you can see that's where it's going to go.
And then put the BR.
So now we should be looking pretty hot and cool.
There we go.
Okay.
That's looking cool.
But now I've got another idea.
Do you want to know what it is you do?
Or.
You sound like you're absolutely fascinated about my other idea.
My idea is.
Okay, now I've got two good ideas.
My first one is.
Let's put some things in bold as well.
We might be the names in bold.
Yeah, let's go with the names, because I can make them stand out because they're still getting a little
lost there.
Okay.
So we're going to use italics and bold and breaks.
And you can see how these all start to stack up.
So we've got this little section.
Just go B.
So it's the B tag.
So some of the tags are really obvious.
You know I for italics B for bold.
Again opening bold where you want it to go.
The ending bold tag.
But all this time notice that the p the paragraph tag is what encapsulates the entire paragraph.
So we set it at the start that the paragraph is the entire piece.
So within it you can have breaks, you can have bold italics and many others.
So we're now going to bold each of our gentlemen's names okay.
So gentlemen, be prepared to be bold.
There we go.
Yeah.
Save it.
Refresh.
And now you'll notice.
Yeah.
Sweet sweet sweet sweet.
So we can bold whatever we want.
Yeah, but.
Good idea.
Yeah, but, but, but I reckon we could over go one better than this.
How's that?
I'll tell you what.
I've got some cool quotes and quotes.
I've got some cool.
We've got quotes.
I've read enough quotes.
Um, movies.
I mean, if I were to ask you, Joshua, you know, if I'd ask you, what would you say is your best,
um, movie that's about education, learning and that sort of thing.
Best movies?
Yeah.
No, just give me one.
One.
Okay.
Um.
Uh.
So many, so many, so many.
Many.
There are quite a few, but I haven't seen Freedom Riders.
I know quite a good one.
Okay, that's a cool one.
So let's say what we want to now do is we want to, like, uh, put a list of education movies.
So we're going to say, uh, what we say our top it.
However you spell it education movies.
Right now, we we could do the whole bold thing and everything, but that's not going to.
So what do you think?
Let's let's just give it like an inch or two.
Not too big, not too small.
Okay.
So we looked at headers earlier.
So H2 is ahead of top.
So here we're going to use a second level header.
So it's not too dramatically big.
Uh let's let's take a look at what that's looking like there.
Okay.
That's not too bad.
I mean what we could do is just to show that we actually remember the fact that line 19 has got nothing
on.
It doesn't mean that line 19 has got nothing on it.
We could put a break there if we wanted, uh, which would just give us a little bit of a space between,
you know, there we go.
So let's move down one.
Okay.
So which was that?
What was that one you were saying?
Uh.
Freedom writers.
So now, if I just put it like that, what's going to happen?
It's probably not going to turn out so well, is it?
No.
Okay.
It's there, but that's not good.
We we sort of want to like.
Well, let's think of some other movies and let's put, let's get maybe our top three.
How about our top three?
Uh, top three.
Uh, you guys out there, you're watching, uh, what are your top three education movies?
What's that?
Sir?
Sorry, sir.
What, love.
Oh, sorry.
I know you're saying.
Ah.
Oh.
To sir.
With love.
Yeah, that.
That's a great one.
Okay.
So, uh.
To sir.
With love.
Uh, yes.
To sir.
With love.
A beautiful friendship that's not actually a French movie.
Okay.
My my my top favorite.
You want to know what my one is?
This is the movie that rocked the world.
This is the movie.
Besides education movies, this one is super cool.
God.
Baby!
Did you recognize it?
The famous line Carpe diem from the movie Dead Poets Society.
Oh, yes.
That was a famous Robin Williams movie, Dead Poets society.
Right.
Fantastic.
Okay, so those are our top horror.
It's not a horror.
That's where he's like, this famous scene, and.
And he's looking at this photograph on the wall in the you know, it's from like 200 years ago, 180
and all the kids are dead, obviously.
And as they lean closer, lean closer.
And as they all lean closer, he goes.
And they turn around and look at the teacher and think he's mad.
But what does carpe diem?
Seize the moment.
Says, gentlemen, those people are pushing up the daisies.
You still got life ahead of you.
Who can make a difference?
Right.
We're being sidetracked here, but here we go.
Okay, ugly.
Joshua, what's going on?
What's going on?
Okay, so obviously we haven't got put any tags in, so just so we could use, we could use breaks and
stuff, but we actually want them as like little, little bullet points don't we.
Yeah.
Okay.
So so we don't use we taught you we asked you to look on what?
This list.
What what our list.
What how what are our hours?
Yeah.
Did you did you do that?
Remember you said go and look at what Lee is.
It's a list.
Did you go?
Did you do it?
I hope you did.
Okay, so here we're going to use the tag.
Yeah.
So what is this about, Josh?
What are we hoping is going to happen by itself?
Well, just it's just basically a list element.
So if you have something in LA, it's going to be like okay, that's an element of a certain type of
list.
So we've got all of those.
Okay.
So we've got three in this list.
So we go across and have a little look.
Okay.
Yeah.
They've got like a little bulleted point list.
So we know that they're all a part of some sort of list.
It's not specific list.
That's why it's you'll see.
Now we've only got just the list.
What do you mean to really do is put all which means ordered list or an unordered list.
Yeah.
We'll do a ul.
So okay.
So what we mean to really do is put you owls which means unordered list which is our bullet points.
And this is going to this means that all of these words right here are meant to be together.
These are all part of our unordered list.
So it's like with our paragraph, um, opening and closing for a paragraph that says that's the start
and that's the end.
The same thing applies with an unordered list a ul.
There's the start and there's the end.
It means that all of these belong to that one unordered list.
So there are two parts to this list is each item in the list.
UL says it's an unordered list, so go and have a little squares.
You will now see.
It knows that these all hang together.
There we go.
It's just indented properly because it knows this is a list.
But you know what?
To me some of those those are top three education movies.
But they're not just points I actually want to say, actually, in my view, this is my I don't know
which is your favorite, but it doesn't really matter because I am going to be the one typing now,
and I think that is the the best, but I don't want it just to appear at the top.
I want it to be one, two, three.
So what's the deal with that?
Okay, so you are unordered list.
If we just make an ordered list, you know, as simple as that.
It's going to be an ordered list now.
So so we've changed UL to ol unordered list to ordered list and dang Dead poets society.
Number one, they have a rocket.
And there we have it.
Our top three education movies.
Copy.
Okay.
Yeah.
So we've got a nice a nice list there.
No, I don't have to push it too much.
Our list.
Um, yeah, that's pretty cool.
Yeah.
So we can you can see it is very small compared to that one.
So obviously if you want, we could change all of the sizes.
I'll let you do that.
You can look through all of the headers the H3.
You can try and make it bold just to get it nice and exactly how you want it.
Right.
So there, we've done some really cool things.
Uh, in looking at, uh, our coding, we've getting quite involved and develop.
Now you can see we're using multiple types of tags and it's over to you to have a little trial.
Why don't you try and see if you can set up a fun little site, a little page like that, with something
that's important to you, maybe education quotes or recipe quotes or movie quotes or life quotes, whatever
you like.
Over to you.